questions = {
        1 : "question" : "What is War Machine's first name?",
            "answer" : "james"
        },  
        2 : "question" : "What country is the scarlet witch from?",
            "answer" : "sokovia"
        },
        3 : "question" : "What is the first name of Tony Stark's daughter?",
            "answer" : "morgan"
        },
        4 : "question" : "Peter Quill's father is considered what type of being?",
            "answer" : "Cellestial"
        },
        5 : "question" : "What was the acronym for the agency that imprisoned Loki?",
            "answer" : "TVA"
        },
        6 : "question" : "What city was Steve Roger's from",
            "answer" : "brooklyn"
        },
        7 : "question" : "What type of doctor is Michael Morbius?",
            "answer" : "biochemist"
        },
        8 : "question" : "On what planet does the soul stone reside?",
            "answer" : "volmir"
        },
        9 : "question" : "What fruit is Pepper Potts allergic to?",
             "answer" : "strawberries"
        ,
        10 : "question" : "What is the Winter Soldiers middle name?",
            "answer" : "buchanan"
        }
}   
